John A. Dix Collection
John A. Dix Collection
- Correspondence
  - 1873, 4 outgoing letters, 3 incoming letters (one written to E. Pierrepont by J. Wadsworth with a message to Dix from Pierrepont at the bottom) (Sc 86)
  - 1874, 9 outgoing letters (Sc 86)
  - 1875, 5 outgoing letters (Sc 86)
  - 1876, 3 outgoing letters (Sc 86)
  - 1877, 4 outgoing letters (Sc 86)
  - Dix, Catherine M., undated; 3 outgoing letters to E. Pierrepont (Sc 86)
  - Dix, John W., 5 Oct 1874; 1 outgoing letter to E. Pierrepont (Sc 86)
  - Series of letters and documents, 1861-1864; Many letters are to Salmon P. Chase, relating to the removal of Timothy Browne Dix from the Warehouse Department of Boston Customs (Sc 86)
- Writings
  - Excerpt from an agricultural address, 1851 (Sc 86)
- Memorabilia
  - Illustrations, 2 (Sc 86)
  - General orders #43 in observation of Dix's funeral, Apr 22 1879; issued by E.D. Townsend (Sc 86)
Selected Index to Correspondence
Aspinwall, Lloyd 22 Oct 1872
Bishop, Edward 15 Jun 1831
Bowman, A. H. 30 Apr 1864
Bronson, Greene C. 27 May 1853
Capen, Nahum 11 Oct 1860 2 Oct 1868
Cheney, Theseus Apoleon 25 Nov 1874
Cullum, George Washington 7 Aug 1861
Doolittle, James Rood 13 Jul 1866
Feuchtwanger, Lewis 15 Feb 1836
Fish, Hamilton 15 Nov 1848 24 Dec 1853
Flagg, Azariah Cutting 21 Apr 1847
Guthrie, James 25 May 1853 27 Jun 1853
Hopkins, N. K. 23 Dec 1873
King, Rufus 7 Jan 1867
Lawrence, John L. 30 Jun 1849
Lincoln, Frederic Walker 14 Jun 1865
McCall, Henry Strong 26 Nov 1844
McClellan, George Brinton 19 Aug 1861
McClelland, R. 23 May 1853
Mason, Charles 22 Nov 1852
Mason, John Young 22 Jun 1847
Minturn, Robert Bowne 22 May 1850
Morgan, John Jordan 7 Sep 1845
Morgan, John Jordan (Mrs.) 16 Aug 1848
Partridge, Theodore 13 Jun 1831 (incoming) 21 Jun 1831 (outgoing on verso)
Pasko, Wesley Washington 7 Dec 1876
Paulding, James Kirke 14 Jul 1838
Pell, Duncan 22 Oct 1863
Pellew, Henry E. 7 Apr 1877
Pierrepont, Edwards 26 Feb 1869 17 Jul 1861 6 Dec 1861 10 Dec 1861 24 Dec 1861 24 Jan 1862 4 Feb 1862 20 Apr 1862 22 Apr 1862 2 May 1862 23 May 1862 10 Jun 1862 27 Jun 1862 (with Ludlow enc.) 27 Jun 1862 4 Jul 1862 13 Jul 1862 21 Jul 1862 24 Jul 1862 10 Aug 1862 6 Sep 1862 15 Sep 1862 31 Oct 1862 3 Nov 1862 14 Nov 1862 24 Nov 1862 19 Apr 1863 5 May 1863 6 May 1863 ? 1864 ? 1864 ? 1864 22 Sep 1865 1 Mar 1866 9 July 1866 15 Dec 1866 26 Feb 1867 11 Apr 1867 12 Nov 1867 6 Feb 1868 28 Feb 1868 31 Aug 1868 28 Nov 1868 1 Oct 1869 18 Aug 1871 7 Sep 1871 23 Nov 1871 16 Apr 1872 26 Sep 1872 25 Dec 1872 30 Apr 1873 11 May 1873 (incoming note to Dix at bottom of J. Wadsworth letter) 8 Dec 1873 14 Dec 1873 2 Apr 1874 23 Apr 1874 30 Jun 1874 17 Oct 1874 25 Nov 1874 26 Nov 1874 11 May 1875 6 Sept 1875 6 Sept 1875 15 Sep 1875 29 Jan 1876 2 Jun 1876 23 May 1877
Prince, Le Baron Bradford 20 Mar 1877
Schofield, John McAllister 1 Feb 1869
Seeger, Ferdinard 28 Mar 1877
Smith, Caleb Blood 6 Mar 1861
Stebbins, Charles 22 Nov 1845
Stebbins, Henry George 14 Sep 1871
Sumner, Charles 28 Jan 1861
Towle, George Makepeace 18 Jun 1867 11 Jan 1868 21 Oct 1868
Townsend, Edward Davis 12 Aug 1861
Tuckerman, Charles Keating 18 Jan 1862
Wadsworth, James 11 May 1873 (incoming)
Washburne, Elihu Benjamin 7 Aug 1867
Weed, Thurlow 17 Oct 1874
Woodford, Stewart Lyndon 1 May 1873 (incoming)